Chester Alan Arthur Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Series 5: Addition II, 1882 (Box 4:19)
  - Letter, Arthur to Sutherland, 1882 (Box 4:19)
Garrison, Curtis W., List of Manuscript Collections in the Library of Congress to July 1931 (Washington, 1932), p. 215.
Hamer, Philip M., ed., A Guide to Archives and Manuscripts in the United States (New Haven, 1961), p. 85, 416, 492.
Howe, George F., Chester A. Arthur, A Quarter-Century of Machine Politics (New York, 1957), p. 292.
Powell, C. Percy, List of Manuscript Collections Received in the Library of Congress July 1931 to July 1938 (Washington, 1939), p. 17.
"The Present Status of Presidential Papers," Manuscripts, VIII (Fall 1955), 14.
Rowland, Buford, "The Papers of the Presidents," American Archivist, XIII (July 1950), 206; reprinted in Autograph Collectors' Journal, III (Summer 1951), 49.
Shelley, Fred, "The Chester A. Arthur Papers," Library of Congress Quarterly Journal of Current Acquisitions, 16 (May 1959), 115-22.
U.S. Library of Congress, Handbook of Manuscripts in the Library of Congress (Washington, 1918), p. 31.